tmssoftware.com 2019-11-30

# TMS Software | Online orders

### Privacy & security

**Data protection**

tmssoftware.com appreciates your interest in its products and your visit to this website. Your privacy is important to us and we want you to feel comfortable visiting our site, using our products, being our customer. The protection of your privacy in the processing of your personal data is an important concern to which we pay special attention during our business processes. Personal data collected during visits to our websites are processed by us according to the legal provisions valid for the countries in which the websites are maintained. Our data protection policy is also based on the data protection policy applicable to tmssoftware.com. 

**tmssoftware.com Data Protection Policy**

The tmssoftware.com website may include links to other websites which are not covered by this privacy statement. 

**Collection and processing of personal data**

When you visit our website, our web server does not store any details of your visit. The only information gathered is the information gathered by Google Analytics. We refer to the Google Analytics terms of servive and privacy policy : https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html 

**Use and passing on of personal data and limitation of use to specific circumstances**

tmssoftware.com uses your personal data only to the extent necessary for the purpose of technical administration of the website, for customer management, for product surveys, and for marketing. 

Personal data is transferred to state organizations and authorities only within the scope of mandatory national provisions of law. We have placed our employees, agencies and dealers under a duty of confidentiality. 

**Scope of data**

tmssoftware.com is only storing the absolute minimum data for identifying customers and purchased products. The data stored is limited to: Company name (when applicable), customer name, customer email address, name of product(s) purchased, date of purchase and account login code. To facilitate an easy login on the website, a cookie is used with an access token for the website. No other data is stored in the cookie or other browser storage. 

**Exchange of data**

tmssoftware.com does not exchange any of our customer data with other parties. All information is treated with full confidentiality. tmssoftware.com employees contracts have a clause governing confidentiality and security policy. 

**Infrastructure**

tmssoftware.com servers are only in offices Belgium and at a hosting company Germany. tmssoftware.com has a GDPR compliant Data Processing Agreement (DPA) with the hosting company. All servers, machines, devices at tmssoftware.com are password protected and in locked rooms. 

**Opt-in**

tmssoftware.com applies an opt-in policy for every form of using your data to contact you. Without your opt-in, tmssoftware.com will never send you unsollicited email. 

**Choice**

We would like to use your data to inform you about our products and services and, if applicable, to ask you about them. Of course, participation in such activities is voluntary. If you do not wish to take part, you can notify us at any time so that we can exclude your data accordingly. 

**Newsletter**

Our website can be used to subscribe to newsletters. The data provided during the newsletter registration will be used only for the purposes of sending out the newsletter, provided you have not consented to other use. You can cancel the subscription at any time by using the unsubscribe option provided in the newsletter. 

**tmssoftware account access**

Customers of tmssoftware.com have a user account to log in to our website and have access to purchased products and support. 

**Email**

Emails sent to tmssoftware.com are treated by the tmssoftware.com team only. It is the tmssoftware.com policy to not forward or share emails with 3rd parties unless their is a consent of the person who sent the email. Emails and the data it can contain related to support cases are stored till the support case is resolved. When the support case is resolved, the data is permanently deleted. 

**Forum**

The tmssoftware.com support forum is a public visible forum. When using the support forum, the customer agrees that the support question is shown in relationship with the person name. No other information than the name and number of support questions asked is publicly displayed. 

**Cookies**

The tmssoftware.com website only uses cookies for identifying returning customers and facilitating automatic login. Cookies do not contain any personal information and are just an access token. 

**Security**

tmssoftware.com uses technical and organizational security measures to protect the data supplied by you and managed by us against manipulation, loss, destruction, and access by third parties. Our security measures are continually improved in line with technological developments. 

**Right to information**

On request, tmssoftware.com or the representative responsible for you will inform you in writing as soon as possible and in accordance with applicable law whether and what personal data relating to you has been stored by us. If you are registered as a user, we also enable you to view the data yourself and, if applicable, to delete or amend it. If incorrect information is stored despite our efforts to ensure that data is accurate and up to date, we will correct it at your request. 

**Questions**

If you have any further questions about the processing of your personal data, you can contact tmssoftware.com who, along with the team, is available should you have any requests for information, suggestions or complaints.
